Abhi Patel

Gandhinagar, Gujarat, India



abhipatel33360@gmail.com



9624346807



linkedin.com/in/abhipatel31

Summary

Finance, AI and ML Enthusiast, Pursuing B.Tech in Information and communication technology from PDEU, Gandhinagar.

In pursuit of challenging assignments that would facilitate the maximum utilization and application of my skills and expertise in making a positive difference to the organization.

Experience



Operations Manager

Smytten

May 2022 - Jul 2022 (3 months)

Developed warehouse design by planning layout, product flow, and product handling systems.

Campus Ambassador

MyCaptain

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021 (2 months)

Helped Mycaptain To get Reach to My collage.

Made Portfolio Website from HTML,CSS and JS

abhipatel.in

Mar 2022 - Present (5 months +)

Made Portfolio website.

A Campus Ambassador

Aparoksha, IIIT Allahabad

Feb 2020 - Mar 2020 (2 months)

Campus Ambassador at Aparoksha, IIIT Allahabad

Education



Adarsh Vidyalaya High School - India

10th and 12th, Mathematics

2016 - 2019

Got 86.5 Percentage in 10th and 73.07 Percentage in 12th

Pandit Deendayal Energy University (PDEU)

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information and communication Technology 2019 - 2023

Abhi Patel - page 1

Pursuing B.Tech in Information and communication technology

Current CPI - 9.16

Licenses & Certifications

- C++ Language Workshop MyCaptain
- C language Workshop MyCaptain

Skills

Financial Analysis • Web Development • Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Microsoft Excel • Business Analysis • Software Development